occonnect.com 2018-07-15

# OC Connect Privacy Policy

We value our privacy and we respect your right to yours. We don't ask for any information we don't absolutely need to know and we don't share any information provided by our visitors with any third parties or use it for any sort of "marketing purposes". 

We never ask children we know to be under the age of thirteen for any personal information whatsoever without express permission from their parent or guardian.

Our server does record each visitor's IP address, which is a number assigned to an individual computer so that the servers it contacts know where to send data. The only information available in an IP number is generally, the name of the user's Internet Service Provider and possibly the city they're connecting from. IP numbers can only be used to identify individual users by the ISP's issuing them. We use IP numbers to get a general idea of where our visitors are from. That's all we need to know. Other than that, our only use for IP numbers would be to report the occasional troublemaker to his or her provider.

Any other information provided to us, such as e-mail address, home address or telephone number is done so voluntarily and we never ask for any information that isn't relevant to the situation in which we're asking for it. An example would be requiring an e-mail address on a link submission form so we can verify the submission or contact the person if we have any questions.

Some of our pages use cookies. They reside on the user's computer and the information contained in them is only used by the application that issued it. Our message boards use them to remember the time and date of a user's last visit and the name they may have posted under. Our survey uses one to deter people from voting more than once. Many sites use cookies to track their visitors' usage patterns. We don't. 

If a user chooses to refuse our cookies, they can still use the message boards, but without the convenience of the program remembering their name or telling them how many messages have been posted since their last visit. A cookie cannot contain any personal information not provided by the user and can only be accessed by the site that issued it.

Some of our content is provided by third parties. We have no control over their privacy policies or those of the sites we link to. Once you've left our domain, we take no responsibility for the security of your personal information. We recommend that you read each site's privacy policy, or if one isn't provided, that you contact the site administrator about any concerns you may have before providing any personal information.

_Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements_

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

If you have any questions about this policy, please feel free to [contact us](mailto:webmaster@occonnect.com).
